findhotel.net 2017-03-03

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy (available in English only)

##### Consent to our Privacy Policy

Access to the FindHotel website is conditional on your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. By using our website, you consent to this Privacy Policy. As new things are always happening in the online world, we will update our Privacy Policy to reflect these changes. Your continued use of the website following an amendment to the Privacy Policy will confirm your acceptance of these revisions. 

Our business is essentially a search engine for hotels and as such we present content and actively engage with trusted third party companies, who in turn, can present dynamic content to our users. Should you navigate away from our site, third party sites will include different Privacy Policies and our FindHotel Privacy Policy will no longer apply.

##### Protecting your privacy

At FindHotel we are committed to the protection of your personal information while you are on our site. We do not collect any personal or sensitive information about you. That includes information or opinions about your health, political affiliations, sexual preferences, religious beliefs, racial or ethnic origin or other such private information.

##### What information we collect and how do we use it

FindHotel may collect information from its users at several different points on our website. We may collect and process the following information about you:

IP Details  
We may collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system, browser type, referring URLs, page views and access times. This information is used for analyzing trends, tracking user movement and system administration. This is statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify you as an individual – we do not collect personally identifiable information and such as your name, address or telephone number. The only personal information that FindHotel may collect is the email address you provide us if you subscribe to our newsletter.

Location Data  
When you open the FindHotel website on a mobile phone or other electronic device we may obtain information about your current geographical location. We may use such data only for the purpose of suggesting hotels that are nearest to you at that time.

Cookies  
For you to get the most from the user experience on the FindHotel website, we collect certain information or “cookies”. Cookies are used for the website to send certain information to your browser and for your browser to return the information at a later time. What this means is that when you browse the FindHotel website in the future, your browser will send us data about your previous activity on our website in order for you to get an optimum user experience. This information does not contain personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number. FindHotel may use cookies to serve specific and targeted content.

Most browsers accept cookies automatically. Your browser may have settings so you can refuse cookies. De-activating cookies may mean that you will no longer be able to enjoy the full operational capabilities of the website and you may not be able to see information that is directly relevant to you. 

Personal Information  
The only personal information that FindHotel may collect is the email address you provide us if you subscribe to our newsletter. We will use this information solely for the purpose of sending you our weekly newsletter, and occasional special offers and deals from FindHotel. As we do not want to send you unwanted email, you can opt-out from our mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in every mail we send. In addition to this, if you contact us we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

Sharing information with other websites  
Subject to this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose any information to companies that are not affiliated with our business without your consent in writing, unless otherwise required by law, or unless such disclosure is, in our opinion, reasonably necessary to protect its rights or property, or to avoid injury to any person.

We can use the collected information for remarketing purposes for any of our brands, including FindHotel and Etrip. These brands are owned by the same company Findhotel B.V.

If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us.
